这样承诺病人明智吗?
I wonder if that's a wise thing...
尤其是精神病患
to be promising patients in a psychiatric facility.
你错了  马克
No, no, no, Mark.
无论对谁  我都清楚表明
I made it clear to each and every one of them,
只能带一个人跟我回去
I can only take one person back with me when I return.
回去?
Return?
不要误会
Mark, don't get me wrong.
你是对我非常好
I mean, you've been very hospitable.
医者父母心
Hospital. Hospitable.
不过时间到了  我不走不行
But my time here is almost up, and I can't wait to get back. Back?
回去?  回K派克斯?
Back? To K-PAX?
当然  还有哪里
Yes, of course. Where else?
你打算回K派克斯?
You're planning to return to K-PAX.
你又在重复我的话  我会先北上
You're repeating yourself again, Mark. Yes, I have one trip to take up north,
然后再回K派克斯
and then I am planning on returning to K-PAX.